嘿  我都打包好可以走了
Hey! l'm all packed and ready to go.
没错
That's right.
爹地跟乔伊叔叔今天要出门去
Daddy and Uncle Joey are going on a trip today.
我们要去参加一个在巴巴多斯的研讨会
We're going to a conference in Barbados.
对吧  你会说"巴巴多斯"吗
Right? Can you say, ''Barbados''?
巴巴多斯
Barbados.
我觉得要你们
Okay. l've gotta say,
到那么远的
it means so much to me
地方去...
that you guys are coming...
听我的演讲
...all the way over there
对我真是意义重大
to hear me give my speech.
我让要你们高兴一下
And l have a surprise.
我费尽功夫...
l had to pull some strings...
帮大家争取到整个研讨会的通行证
...but l was able to get everyone passes
没错
to the entire conference. That's right!
这些宝贝可以让你们自由参加所有的
These babies will get you into
古生物学演讲或是研讨会
all the paleontology lectures and seminars.
你有什么东西
Do you have anything
是可以让我们不用参加的吗
that will get us out of them?
我们真的很兴奋要听你的演讲
We're excited to hear the speech,
但是其他的时间...
but the rest of the time...
我们想要做一些岛上活动
...we're gonna want to do island stuff.
大卫或许会想要听几场演说
David will probably want to hear a few lectures.
没错  因为他是科学家
Right, because he's a scientist.
不  不
No, no.
他在明斯克待了八年
He's been in Minsk for eight years.
如果他在阳光下太久...
lf he gets too much direct sunlight...
他会死的
...he'll die.
好的  我们最好出发了
Okay, we'd better go.
是吗
Yeah?
那我们明天见
So we'll see you guys tomorrow.
好的  明天见
All right, let's do it.
跟查莉一起飞行五个小时
A five-hour flight with Charlie,
喝几杯酒...
have a couple drinks...
在毛毯下
...get under that blanket
做一些自然会发生的事
and do what comes natural.
那是毛毯  乔伊
lt's a blanket, Joe,
不是隐形大衣
not a cloak of invisibility.
《老友记》  第九季 第23、24集  巴巴多斯  我们来了
Friends S09E23E24 The One In Barbados
哇  这地方真漂亮
Wow, this place is beautiful!
瞧瞧这么多古生物学家
Look at all these paleontologists!
我知道
l know.
明天游泳池旁一定
There are gonna be some pasty folks
有许多苍白的人
by the pool tomorrow.
我的天啊
My God,
我不敢相信你在这里
l can't believe you're here!
我想我被认出来了
l think l've been recognized.
这常常发生的
This happens all the time.
盖勒博士  我真是你的超级粉丝
Dr.Geller? l am such a huge fan.
这倒是从来没有发生过
That never happens.
我多年以来一直很注意你的研究
l've been following your career for years.
我等不及要听你的演说了
l can't wait for your keynote speech.
哇  你太过奖了
Wow! This is very flattering.
我很想要你的签名
l would love your autograph.
哦  当然
Well, sure.
"亲爱的..."
''Dear...?''
莎拉
Sarah.
"莎拉  我喜欢（挖掘）你"
''Sarah. l dig you.''
"罗斯·盖勒博士上"
''Dr. Ross Geller.''
哇  真是太谢谢你了
Oh, thank you so much.
不客气  莎拉  让我帮你介绍一下
Sure. Sarah, l'd like you to introduce you
我同事  魏勒教授
to my colleague, Professor Wheeler.
这位是乔伊·崔比安尼
And this is Joey Tribbiani.
你是古生物学家吗
Are you a paleontologist?
不  天啊  不  我是演员
No, God, no, no. l'm an actor.
你或许有看过我演的一出小戏
You probably recognize me from a little show
叫做 《那个我们的日子》
called The Days of Our Lives.
老兄  只是《我们的日子》
Dude, it's just Days of Our Lives.
没有"那个"
There's no ''the.''
好的  罗斯
Okay, Ross.
天啊  你...是啊
Boy, you.... Yeah.
不  我扮演德雷克·罗曼瑞医生
No, no. l play Dr. Drake Ramoray.
我很抱歉  我家没有电视
l'm sorry. l don't own a TV.
你家没有电视
You don't own a TV?
那你家的家具是以什么为中心摆放的
What's all your furniture pointed at?
大卫  你可以帮个忙吗
David, can you help me?
我正在跟钱德勒解释
l'm trying to explain to Chandler
飞机是怎么飘浮在空中的
how a plane stays in the air.
当然
Certainly.
那是伯努利原理加上...
That's a combination of Bernoulli's Principle...
牛顿第三运动定律
...and Newton's third law of motion.
知道了吗
See?
是啊
Yeah.
跟你说的 "跟风有关的"
That's the same as,
是一个意思
''lt has something to do with wind.''
我要去为这次旅行
l'm gonna go pick up
买几样东西
a few things for the trip.
我也应该走了
l should go too.
明天你们要一起搭计程车到机场吗
Now, tomorrow do you guys want to share a cab to the airport...
难忘往日情怀脱口而出吗
That's a blast from the past, huh?
不  没关系的  无心之过
No, it's okay. Honest mistake.
那真的不代表什么
lt really doesn't mean anything.
我是说  你知道的...
l mean, you know...
莫妮卡也常常
...Monica refers to Chandler
把钱德勒叫理查德
as Richard all the time.
她有吗
She does?
你快给我走吧
Let's get you out of here.
至少你也拖我下水了
Well, at least you took me down with you.
我很抱歉
l'm so sorry.
我只是...  我一直在想迈克
l just-- l keep thinking about Mike.
我非常喜欢大卫
l'm crazy about David,
而且我们在一起很开心
and we're having so much fun together.
为什么我会想念迈克
Why? Why do l miss Mike?
这真是...  这会消逝的  对吗
That's just-- That's gonna go away, right?
嗯  我猜是吧  总有一天
Well, l guess. ln time.
是啊
Yeah.
我是说我对理查德的感觉
l mean, my feelings for Richard
都已经消失了
are certainly gone.
你又来了
You just did it again.
是钱德勒
Chandler.
你对钱德勒的感觉
Your feelings for Chandler
都已经消失了
are certainly gone.
天啊  菲比还在想迈克吗
Boy, Phoebe's still pretty hung up on that Mike, huh?
我不会想太多的
l wouldn't read too much into it.
但是女生把你叫成
Still, a girl calls you
她前男友的名字...
by her ex-boyfriend's name...
那不是什么好事  不是吗
...that's not a good thing, right?
大卫  让我先打断你一下
David, let me stop you there.
因为我想我知道这是怎么回事了
Because l think l see where this is going.
我对给人建议不太行
l'm not very good at giving advice.
如果你想得到建议
See, if you want advice,
去找罗斯或者莫妮卡
go to Ross or Monica. Or Joey...
如果你想知道披萨的馅料或是
...for advice about pizza toppings
为何尿尿时有灼热感之类的...  就找乔伊
or a burning sensation when you pee.
很抱歉
l'm sorry,
我只是希望能做点什么
l just wish there was something l could do,
你知道吗
you know?
嗯  你知道菲比...
Well, you know Phoebe--
真的  我们要这样吗
Seriously, we're gonna do this?
很抱歉
l'm sorry,
我只希望我能
l just wish l could make her
让她忘了迈克
forget about Mike already.
菲比跟迈克为什么分手呢
Why did Phoebe and Mike break up?
因为他的鸡鸡太大了
Because his penis was too big.
抱歉  那才是我擅长的事
l'm sorry. That's the kind of thing l do.
他们分手是
They broke up because
因为迈克不想要结婚
Mike didn't want to get married.
如果让菲比知道
What if you let Phoebe know
你对婚姻没有异议呢
you'd be open to marriage?
太棒了  太棒了  我会跟她求婚
That's great. That's great. l'll propose to her.
什么
What?
反正我迟早都会这么做的
l was probably going to do it at some point.
不  我没有说现在
No, l didn't mean now.
为何不呢  这主意太好了
Well, why not? lt's brilliant.
再见  迈克
''Goodbye, Mike.
我们婚礼见  老兄
We'll see you at the wedding, fella.
我们可能也不会 邀请你参加婚礼
Well, we probably won't invite you to the wedding,
但是...
but--''
衷心地谢谢你  钱德勒
Well, thank you, Chandler. Sincerely.
你不用客气
Well, you're welcome.
很高兴能够帮得上忙
Glad l could help.
你认为我该怎么求婚呢
How do you think l should propose?
大卫  我在假装读报纸呢
David, l'm pretending to read here.
抱歉
l'm sorry.
你好吗
Yeah. How you doing?
嘿  你好吗
Hey, how are you?
你说你要穿丁字裤的
You said you were gonna wear a thong.
丁字裤呢
Where's the thong?
我不是说丁字裤
l didn't mean a thong.
我是说夹脚凉鞋
l meant thongs.
你应该要说清楚的
You really should have been more clear about that.
你们不会相信
You're never gonna guess
我在楼下看到谁
who l just saw downstairs.
小甜甜布莱尼
Britney Spears!
是啊  她从来不会错过
Yeah. She never misses
这些研讨会的
these conferences.
我刚刚看到肯尼斯·史华兹博士
No, l just saw Dr. Kenneth Schwartz!
喔  我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我知道
l know!
你有跟他说话吗
Did you talk to him?
是喔  我要跟
Oh, yeah. What am l
肯尼斯·史华兹说什么呢
gonna say to Kenneth Schwartz?
你可以说
You could say,
"嗨  肯尼
''Hey, Kenny,
为什么你不是小甜甜布莱尼呢  "
how come you're not Britney Spears?''
你准备好要走了吗
You ready to go?
你现在就要走了吗
You're gonna go now?
我以为我们可以在一起坐会闲聊呢
l thought we could hang out.
我不行  我整天都有研讨会
l can't. l have seminars all day.
我答应罗斯我会看看他的演说稿
l promised Ross l'd look at his speech.
但是或许我们晚点可以用进晚餐
But maybe we could have dinner later?
在阳台外面
Out on the balcony?
会很浪漫的
lt'll be romantic.
你可以穿丁字裤吗
Will you wear a thong?
你穿我就穿
l will if you will.
你谈成了一笔奇怪的交易
You got yourself a very weird deal.
我很好  我晚餐已经有安排了
l'm good. l have dinner plans.
你一个人可以吗
So you gonna be okay?
是的  可以
Yeah, yeah.
我有很多事可以做
l got tons of stuff l could do.
我要去海滩  去游泳
l'm gonna hit the beach, go swimming.
乔伊  你知道外面什么情况吗
Joe, have you looked outside?
没有  为什么呢
No. Why?
天啊
Oh, man.
这里有室内游泳池
There's an indoor pool.
你可以在那边游泳
You could swim there.
是啊
Yeah.
我没有要游泳  我是要去挖洞的
l wasn't gonna swim. l was gonna dig a hole.
迈克那件事真是有趣
That Mike thing was interesting.
我不知道...
l don't know what's gonna happen...
菲比跟大卫之间会发生什么事
...with Phoebe and David.
我知道  想要个提示吗
l do. Want a hint, huh?
我知道（我愿意）
l do.
我知道
好的  我可以感到
Okay, l'm sensing this is
这是什么文字游戏的
some kind of wordplay...
因为你已经有点
...because you are pink
无法控制的兴奋发红了
with barely controlled glee.
大卫要跟菲比求婚了
David's gonna propose to Phoebe.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
因为我们本来在谈
Because we were talking about ways
有哪些他可以赢过迈克的方式
he could beat Mike...
而我告诉他
...and l told him Phoebe
菲比想要结婚
wanted to get married.
钱德勒  我们已经谈过了
Chandler, we have talked about this.
你不可以给别人建议的
You are not supposed to give people advice!
你不能说一些什么不适宜的笑话就好了吗
Couldn't you have made some inappropriate joke?
我说了
l did!
一个鸡鸡的笑话
A penis one!
说明一下
Just so l know,
我说的有什么不对的呢
what was so wrong about what l said?
他们才交往几个星期而已
They've only been going out for a few weeks.
菲比还无法忘记迈克
Phoebe is completely hung up on Mike.
我想她会拒绝的
l mean, she'll say no...
然后大卫会心碎
...David's heart will be broken,
他们会很难复合
it'll be too hard for them to recover...
菲比最后又落得孤零零一个人
...and then Phoebe will end up alone again.
天啊  真是糟糕的建议
Man, that's some bad advice.
感谢上帝你们来了
Oh, hey. Thank God. You guys are here.
怎么了
What's going on?
这里的一切都不对劲
Everything is upside-down here.
整天都在下雨  没有人看电视
lt rains all day long and nobody watches TV,
而且罗斯还很有名气
and Ross is famous.
我不想要惊动大家...
l don't want to alarm anybody...
但是莫妮卡的头发
...but Monica's hair is twice as big as it was
比下飞机时大了一倍
when we landed.
好了  当我去高湿度地区的时候...
Okay. When l go places with high humidity...
头发就会比较蓬松  好吗
...it gets a little extra body, okay?
那就是为什么我们的蜜月照
That's why our honeymoon photos
看起来是我跟戴安娜·罗斯
look like me and Diana Ross.
我带你们去登记入驻
l'll show you guys where to check in.
亲爱的
Oh, honey?
一定要弄张超大尺寸的床
Can you make sure we get a king-size bed?
大卫  也帮我们弄一张
Oh, David, get one for us too. Oh,
还有看看他们有没有心型的床
and see if they have a heart-shaped one.
天花板上要有镜子
And with mirrors on the ceiling.
还有确定我们的房间
And make sure our room
不要在他们的隔壁
isn't next to theirs.
喔  你们真幸运
Oh, you guys are so lucky
有人陪你们到这里
you're here with people.
这是个很浪漫的地方
You know, it's just such a romantic place.
我只希望可以跟一个男人共度
l just wish l could share it with a guy.
不是乔伊
Not Joey.
不是乔伊  不是
Not Joey. No.
我只是在垂涎钱德勒
l was just lusting after Chandler.
是啊  没错
Yeah, right.
我今晚要跟菲比求婚了
So.... l'm proposing to Phoebe tonight.
今晚
Tonight?
订婚戒指不是应该要有钻石的吗
lsn't an engagement ring supposed to have a diamond?
哦  找到了
Oh, there it is.
是啊  一个失败的科学家
Yes, well, being a failed scientist
并没有你想的赚的多
doesn't pay quite as well as you might think.
那是七十分之一克拉
That's one-seventieth of a carat.
而且透明度非常差
And the clarity is quite poor.
很好
Nice.
莫妮卡  我可以跟你谈一下吗
Monica, can l talk to you for a second?
好的
Okay.
大卫要在今晚跟菲比求婚
David's gonna propose to Phoebe tonight.
瞧瞧这就是
See what happens
你给别人建议的后果
when you give people advice?
我希望你有告诉他不可以
Well, l hope you told him not to.
那又会是一个建议了
That would be advice!
好的  没关系  让我来处理
Okay, fine. l'll handle this.
菲比
Phoebe?
怎样
Yeah?
我需要跟你谈谈
l need to talk to you.
你要离开你的"至高无上"乐队了吗
Are you leaving the Supremes?
我老公刚给了你男友
Okay, my husband just gave your boyfriend
一个很糟糕的建议
some very bad advice.
大卫今晚要跟你求婚了
David's gonna propose to you tonight.
哇  真的吗
Wow, really?
这实在太棒了
That's fantastic!
什么  你是说真的吗
What? Are you serious?
你想嫁给他
You want to marry him?
那迈克呢
What about Mike?
好的  你要我嫁给迈克是吗
Oh, okay, you want me to marry Mike?
让我们把他塞住嘴巴铐起他来
Let's just gag him and handcuff him...
然后逼他踏上红毯  好吗
...and force him down the aisle, okay?
我已经可以预见到
l can just see it.
"迈克  你愿意娶菲比吗  "
''Mike, do you take Phoebe?''
你知道吗  真是每个女孩的梦想
You know? lt's every girl's dream.
你真的认为
Do you really think
嫁给别人是对的
marrying someone else is the right answer?
当然  听着  最重要的是
Sure. Look, okay, bottom line?
我爱迈克...大卫
l love Mike-- David!
大卫  我爱大卫
David! l love David.
别那样看我
Don't look at me that way,
罗斯安妮·罗莎娜丹娜
Roseanne Roseannadanna.
借由X光断层摄影及电脑成像
''By using CT scans and computer imaging,
我们可以以非常真实的方式...
we can, in a very real way...
将中生代时期带进二十一世纪
...bring the Mesozoic Era into the 21 st century.''
太棒了
lt's great.
你将成为此次研讨会的焦点
You'll be the hit of the conference.
明天还会更好
lt'll be even better tomorrow...
因为我不会一直被乔伊打断...
...because l won't be constantly interrupted by Joey...
一直来检查我枕头上
...checking to see
是不是有放巧克力
if they put chocolates on my pillow yet.
你们好
Hey, guys.
巧克力还没送来
The chocolates aren't here.
该死的
Damn it!
罗斯刚念了他的演讲稿给我听
Ross just read me his speech.
真是精彩
lt's fantastic.
在电脑里面吗
Oh, is it on the computer?
因为我也想读读看
Because l'd love to give it a read.
如果你想要查电子邮件就说吧
lf you want to check your e-mail, just ask.
什么  我可以吗
What? May l?
那个雨是怎么回事呢  盖勒
What's with the rain, Geller?
我是说当我报名恐龙营的时候...
l mean, when l signed up for dino week...
没有人说过现在是雨季
...nobody said anything about it being monsoon season.
雨季是六月到十二月
The wet season is June to December.
现在不是时候  查莉
lt's not the time, Charlie.
哎呀  糟糕  亲爱的上帝  不
Oh, no. No, no! Dear God, no!
怎么了
What,
有人对茶壶的出价比你高吗
did someone outbid you for the teapot?
秘密茶壶
Secret teapot.
你的电脑
Your computer.
我不知道怎么... 一切都不见了
l don't know what-- Everything's gone.
你是什么意思呢
What do you mean?
一定是病毒
Must be a virus.
肯定是把你的硬盘给格了
l think it erased your hard drive.
什么  我的天啊   你干了什么好事
What? Oh, my God. What did you do?
一个我不认识的人寄了封信给我
Someone l don't know sent me an e-mail
然后我打开了它
and l opened it.
为什么  为什么你要打开
Why? Why would you open it?
那上面又没有写"这是病毒"
Well, it didn't say, ''This is a virus.''
那上面写什么
What did it say?
"裸体的..."
''Nude--''
"安娜·库尔尼科娃（网球运动员）的照片"
"Pictures of Anna Kournikova."
我很抱歉
l'm so sorry.
我该怎么办呢
What am l gonna do?
我的讲稿不见了   钱德勒
My speech is gone! Chandler.
没有不见
lt's not gone.
我相信你有列印出来
l'm sure you printed out a copy.
你有印出来吗  对吧
You have a hard copy? Right?
不  我没有
No, l don't!
那你现在一定很气自己
Well, you must be pretty mad at yourself right now.
真的不见了吗
lt's really gone?
是的
Yep.
我想要谢谢你们过来这里...
l'd like to thank you guys for coming down here...
抱怨这场雨
...to complain about the rain
然后毁了我的事业前途
and ruin my career.
我觉得糟透了
l just feel awful.
你的确应该
Yeah, you should.
安娜·库尔尼科娃的裸照
Nude pictures of Anna Kournikova?
她根本没赢过什么主要赛事
She's never even won a major tournament.
我是有试过比莉·珍·金  但是...
Well, l tried Billie Jean King, but--
你知道吗 你跟莫妮卡一样都有那种
You know, you and Monica have the same
我想要杀死你的表情
l'm-gonna-kill-you look.
我通常可以亲她一下
l can usually make it go away
就逃过一劫
by kissing her.
滚出去
Get out.
我工作的电脑
You know, this happens all the time
也常常发生这种事
to my computer at work.
那你怎么办呢
What do you do?
我通常会...
l usually go...
到别人的电脑上玩俄罗斯方块
...play Tetris on somebody else's computer.
我不敢相信发生这种事
l can't believe this is happening.
我明天就要演讲了
l have to give the keynote speech tomorrow.
我要站在所有人面前
l have to stand up in front of all these people.
我要说什么呢
What am l gonna say?
你可以用我背下来
You can use a speech
参加试镜的那段话
l memorized for auditions.
我不认为你在《星际大战》里的独白
l don't think your monologue from Star Wars
可以对我有所帮助
is gonna help me right now.
罗斯  不会有问题的
Ross, we can solve this.
我听过你的演讲
l just heard your speech.
我们可以重新写出来
We can re-create it.
我们有一整晚
We've got all night.
什么  你真的认为我们办得到吗
What, you really think we can do that?
等等
Oh, wait.
乔伊跟我应该要共进晚餐的
Joey and l are supposed to have dinner.
别担心晚餐了
Don't worry about that.
我知道罗斯需要你
l mean, Ross needs you.
瑞秋跟我会留下来尽量帮忙
Rachel and l will stay and help any way we can.
好的  我们来开始吧
All right. Okay, let's do it.
我知道我们一开始
Well, l know we start by
是讨论碳年代测定法的缺点
discussing the shortcomings of carbon dating.
然后我接着解说
And then l move on to
很明显地什么是...
what is clearly the defining moment...
中生代的决定时刻
...of the Mesozoic Era,
原始大陆的分裂  不是吗
the breakup of Pangaea. Hello?
然后接下来是三叠纪的概观
And then there's the overview of the Triassic.
有可能这一切都是在
Any chance any of this happened
很远的银河发生的吗
in a galaxy far, far away?
哈啰
Hello?
好了  迈克
Okay, Mike?
闹够了
Enough is enough.
你爱菲比  而她也爱你
You love Phoebe, and she loves you.
所以不要再说什么
So get over your
不想要结婚的话了
l-never-wanna-get-married thing...
赶快站出来
...and step up!
你是谁
Who is this?
我是莫妮卡  菲比的朋友
This is Monica, Phoebe's friend.
听着  菲比跟大卫复合了
Listen, Phoebe is back with David.
他即将要求婚
He's gonna propose,
而她将会答应 但是我知道
and she's gonna say yes... ...but l know
她真正想要的是跟你在一起
she really wants to be with you.
他要求婚了
He's gonna propose?
很抱歉  你说什么呢
l'm sorry, did you say something?
该死的头发遮住我听不到
l can't hear through all this damned hair!
如果菲比想要嫁给大卫
lf Phoebe wants to marry David,
她就嫁吧
she should.
我不会从中作梗
l'm not gonna stand in the way of that.
你也不应该
Neither should you.
你不用告诉我该怎么做
You don't tell me what to do.
我来告诉你怎么做
l tell you what to do.
打电话给她
Just call her.
她在巴巴多斯的天堂饭店
She's at the Paradise Hotel in Barbados.
对了  既然联系上你了  你也有卷发
And while l've got you, you've got curly hair.
在湿气重的地方你怎么办呢
What do you do in the humidity?
该死的
Damn it!
嗯  我希望你很快乐
Well, l hope you're happy.
我也希望你很快乐  亲爱的
l hope you're happy too, honey.
菲比会答应大卫的求婚
Phoebe's going to say yes to David.
这就是你爱管闲事的结果
That's what happens when you meddling people's lives.
菲比要答应  太棒了
Phoebe's gonna say yes? That's great.
不  一点也不  她还爱着迈克
No, it's not. She's still in love with Mike.
那不会有什么结果的吗
There's no chance that will work?
没有  我已经打过电话了
No, l called.
不会发生的
lt's not gonna happen.
鸡婆  鸡婆
Meddler! Meddler!
如果你不先多管闲事...
lf you hadn't meddled to start with...
那我就不用插手
...then l wouldn't have had to
进来管事了
go in and meddle myself.
不管我们插手多深
No matter how much we meddle,
我们都没有办法补救...
we'll never be able to unmeddle...
你一开始多管闲事惹出来的祸
...the thing that you meddled up in the first place!
这假期真是烂
This vacation sucks!
我好无聊
l'm so bored.
愚蠢的雨
Stupid rain.
我们什么都做不了
We can't do anything.
我带了些书来
Well, l brought some books.
我们可以看书
We could read.
嘿  还没糟糕到那个地步
Hey, it hasn't come to that yet.
嘿  等一下
Hey, hey, hey, don't mind if l do.
对不起  先生
l'm sorry, sir,
这些是给药学研讨会的
these are for the pharmaceutical convention.
你想要去参加研讨会吗
You feel like going to a convention?
我们不行
We can't.
我们不是药剂师
We're not pharmacists.
我知道我们不是...
l know we're not...
但是法兰克·马迭欧跟伊娃...
...but Frank Madaio and Eva....
凯特·米勒
Kate Miller.
就凯特·米勒了
Kate Miller it is.
好的
Okay.
哦  很好...
Oh, good--
而这将是我这周末
And that's the most sex
仅能有的性事了
l'm gonna have this weekend.
如果是这样
Well, in that case,
那我一定得让你感觉好啊
should l make sure it's on real good?
谢谢你
Thank you.
然后你开始谈到
Oh, and then you said that
中生代世纪...
thing about bringing the Mesozoic Era...
带到二十一世纪
...into the 21 st century.
对  就这样吗
Well, yeah. That's it?
天啊  我们办到了
Oh, my God. We did it.
事实上是我办到了  罗斯
Actually, l did it, ross.
你对自己演讲稿的记忆
You remembered shockingly little
真是少到惊人
of your own speech.
是的  但是我倒是用沐浴产品
Yes, but l did make a pyramid
做了个金字塔
out of the bath products.
这真是惊人  谢谢
Oh, this is amazing. Thank you.
真是很谢谢你
Thank you so much.
你的项链真漂亮
That's a pretty necklace.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们来庆祝一下吧
Hey, what do you say we celebrate?
要香槟吗
Champagne?
好啊  软木塞留着
Yeah! Save the cork,
这样我们就可以 把瓶子装满水...
and that way, we can fill the bottle with water...
然后再放回去 他们就不会收钱了
...and put it back so they don't charge you.
我的天啊  我爱你
Oh, my God, l love you.
艾玛这张照片真是可爱
This is such a cute picture of Emma.
而这是你儿子...
And is this your son...
还是你会带在身上
...or just some kid whose picture
某个小男孩照片呢
you bring on vacation?
那是本  我第一次婚姻所生的儿子
That's Ben, my son from my first marriage.
你第一次婚姻
Your first marriage?
是的
Yeah.
你结过不只一次婚吗
You've been married more than once?
没有
No.
那你为什么离婚呢
So why'd you break up?
嗯  因为...
Oh, it was--
很复杂的  她是...
lt's complicated, you know? She was...
同性恋
...gay.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
这实在太酷了
This is so cool!
好的  为这怪事兴奋是很奇怪的事
Okay. Odd thing to get excited about.
不是  只是我曾经跟一个男的订婚过
No, it's just that l was engaged to a guy
而他最后竟然是同志
who turned out to be gay.
嘿  击掌吧
Hey! High-five!
你有没有觉得没有看出端倪
Didn't you feel so stupid
实在是很笨呢
that you didn't see the signs?
我未婚夫总是跟
My fiance was always going on
他的"网球球友"一起度周末
long weekends with his ''tennis partner.''
我老婆有年跟一个朋友
My wife had a workout friend
天天都到健身房健身
she went to the gym with every day for a year.
她也没有变瘦
She didn't get any fitter.
每个人都说"我早就知道了"
Everybody's like, ''l knew all along.''
我知道 如果知道  怎么不告诉我呢
l know. lf you knew, why didn't you tell me?
我是说只要打电话  给个纸条
l mean, call, leave a note.
"嗨  只是过来告诉你 你老婆是同性恋"
''Hi. Just dropped by to say your wife's gay.''
我知道
l know.
然后...
And then--
然后你试着在困境中求生存...
And then you try to make the best of a bad situation...
所以你提出三人行的建议
...so you float the idea of a threesome.
我没有那样做
l didn't do that.
我也没有
Me neither.
谁会知道呢
Well, who knew?
药剂师们真好玩
Pharmacists are fun.
我知道  那位老太太
l know. That old lady at the end
最后都已经准备要带你回家了
was ready to take you home.
这世界的药还是不够的  瑞秋
Not enough pills in the world, Rach.
那你呢  你才是单身的人
What about you, huh? You're the single one.
有没有看到喜欢的人呢
See anybody in there you like?
让我想想
Well, let's see.
那个跟我
There was that really big guy
说过话的大个儿...
that l was talking to...
有着很不错的胸部
...with the really nice breasts.
那在家呢
But what about back home?
有什么吗
Anything going on there?
你有喜欢的人吗
Anybody you like?
没有
No.
有的  你脸红了
There is. You're blushing.
没有  我没有脸红
No, l'm not blushing...
这是晒伤的
...and l'm sunburned.
因为下雨的缘故
From, you know, the rain.
你喜欢某人  告诉我是谁
You like someone. Tell me who.
不  乔伊
No. Joey.
你喜欢谁呢
Who do you like?
你别想轻易躲掉
You're not getting away that easy.
你喜欢谁呢
Who do you like?
乔伊  别这样
Joey, come on!
没什么大不了的  你知道吗
lt doesn't matter, you know?
又不是说会发生什么事
lt's not like anything's gonna happen.
什么  为什么不呢
What? Why not?
瑞秋  有谁你得不到呢
Rach, who can you not get?
好
Okay. Okay.
你真想知道是谁吗
You really want to know who it is?
是的  是谁呢
Yeah. Who is it?
你真的想
Do you?
嗨
Oh, hey.
我才刚留言给你
l just left you a message.
罗斯跟我刚要去吃点东西...
Ross and l were gonna go grab a bite...
但是既然你在这里
...but now that you're here,
我们可以共用晚餐了
we could have that dinner.
没错  当然
Right! Of course.
演讲稿写完了吗
Hey, did you guys finish the speech?
是的  完成了  我们完成了
Yep! We got it. We got it.
非常谢谢
Thank you so much.
我很愉快
l had a great time.
是啊
Yeah.
这还没完
This isn't over,
因为我真的想知道...
because l really want to know--
等一下  等一下
Later. Later.
那我们走吧
So shall we?
好的
Yeah.
Okay.
晚安
Good night.
好的  晚安
Okay, good night.
晚安  罗斯
Good night, Ross.
我不敢相信她会答应大卫
l can't believe she's gonna say yes to David.
她很明显还是爱着迈克
She's clearly in love with Mike.
你看起来这样子
You know, it's very hard to
实在很难把你的话当真
take you seriously when you look like that.
菲比  有些话我要跟你说
Phoebe, l have something l want to say.
天啊  他要开口了
Oh, God, he's gonna do it.
我看不下去  我们走
l cannot watch this. Let's go.
我想我们还有时间
l think we have time.
你有听过他说话吗
Have you heard him talk?
"菲比  我将会很荣幸如果..."
''Phoebe, l would be honored if--''
说快点  大卫
Spit it out, David!
菲比
Phoebe.
你实在是太好了
You're an amazing woman,
我们分开的时候实在无法让人忍受
and the time we spent apart was unbearable.
当然明斯克卫生设施员工的
Of course, the sanitation strikes
罢工让情况更糟
in Minsk didn't help.
当然  好的  是的
Sure. Okay. Yeah.
但是现在我们又一起了
But, well, now that we're together again,
我再也不想分开了
l don't ever want to be apart.
所以...
So to that end....
我的天啊  迈克
Oh, my God, Mike.
事实上  我是大卫
lt's David, actually.
不  迈克在这里
No, Mike's here.
嘿  迈克
Oh, hey, Mike.
嗨  大卫
Hi, David.
钱德勒  莫妮卡... 哇
Chandler. Monic-- Oh!
是湿气
lt's the humidity!
嗨  菲比
Hi, Phoebe.
你在这里做什么呢
What are you doing here?
我有个问题必须要问你
l have a question l need to ask you.
我也有个问题
l have a question
要问她
l was kind of gonna ask her myself.
我了解  但是在你那样做之前
Yeah, l understand, but before you do,
她真的需要先听我说
she really needs to hear this.
好的
Okay.
你要坐我的座位吗
Would you care for my seat as well?
事实上会很好
Actually, yeah, that'd be great.
很公平
Well, that's fair,
你一路这么远赶来
you've had a long trip.
菲比  我爱你
Phoebe, l love you.
在过去几个月里
l've missed you so much
我非常想念你
these last few months.
我原以为我们分开是有好理由的
l thought we were apart for a good reason...
但是我发现
...but l realized that
根本没有够好的理由...
there was no reason good enough...
能够让我不与你
...to keep me from spending
共度下半辈子
the rest of my life with you.
有点毁了我将要说的话
Kind of steps on the toes of what l was going to say.
抱歉  大卫
l'm sorry, David,
但是她真的有需要知道这些
but she really has to know this.
好的  但是之后
All right, when you're through,
我要在外面跟你单挑
l want to see you outside.
如果外面停止下雨的话
lf it stops raining.
你是我遇过最不可思议的女人
You're the most incredible woman l've ever met.
我怎么能够失去你呢
How could l lose you?
我现在并没有戒指
Now, l don't actually have a ring.
我有戒指
l have a ring.
我不会在这时候炫耀  老兄
l wouldn't brag about that, big guy.
但是  菲比...
But, Phoebe...
你愿意嫁给我吗
...will you marry me?
不
No.
我爱你
l love you,
但是我从不需要你求婚
but l never needed a proposal from you.
我只需要知道我们之间是有发展的
l just needed to know we were headed somewhere.
我们是有未来的
That we had a future.
我们可以有任何你想要的未来
We can have any future you want.
好的  我要走了
Okay, well, l'm gonna take off.
大卫  我很抱歉  我好抱歉
David, l'm so sorry. l'm sorry.
让我知道一下  如果我先问了
Just so l know, if l had asked first...?
我有可能会答应
Yeah, l might have said yes,
但是那是不对的
but that would've been wrong.
你不用解释  没关系
Please, you don't have to explain.
我是说  如果我当初没有去明斯克...
l mean, perhaps if l hadn't gone to Minsk...
我们之间可能就没问题了
...things would have worked out for us,
而我也不会毁了我的事业
and l wouldn't have ruined my career.
或是因冻疮而失去那根脚趾
Or lost that toe to frostbite.
这旅行还不错
lt was a good trip.
我现在可以拥抱你吗
ls it okay if l hug you now?
喔  可以
Oh, yes.
就是因为我们的多管闲事  好吗
Because of our meddling! All right?
这样不是很好吗
Oh, isn't this nice?
如此安静  我可以整天都躺在这里
lt's so quiet. l could just lie here all day.
我知道
Oh, l know.
打开窗帘  打开窗帘
Open your drapes! Open your drapes!
我们的房间是相通的还真不错呢
So glad we got adjoining rooms.
太阳出来了
The sun is out!
嘿  记得我看得到的时候吗
Hey! Remember when l had corneas?
赶快去游泳池占位子
Go to the pool and reserve chairs.
我会拿杂志跟防晒乳液
l will get the magazines and the lotion.
罗斯的演讲再四十五分就开始了
Ladies? Ross' speech is in 45 minutes.
不
No!
该死的
Damn it!
墙壁很薄的  你们这些人
Walls are pretty thin, guys.
我们必须考量最近磁共振造影资料
''Then we have to weigh the data from recent MRl scans
与去氧核糖核酸测试资料...
and DNA testing...
而这些对多年来的碳年代
...which call into question information
测定资料收集方式形成了一些疑点
gathered from years of carbon dating.''
瞧瞧那个坐在游泳池畔
Look at the woman sitting out
享受日光浴的女人
by the pool getting tan.
她的皮都有皱纹了
She's all leathery and wrinkled.
我真是忌妒
l'm so jealous!
最后  有最近 许多丰富新物种的发现
''Finally, factor in the profusion of new species recently discovered.
巨兽龙
Giganotosaurus.
阿根廷龙
Argentinosaurus.''
更不用提冷龙
Not to mention Coldsaurus.
而这些只是草食性的
''And that's just the herbivores.
我还没有要提到肉食性的
l'm not even gonna discuss the carnivores.
他们的头都已经是太大了
Their heads are already too big.
这是蛮讽刺的
Which is ironic,
因为他们的大脑却是发育不良的
considering their stunted cerebral development.''
真的吗
Really?
但是撇开玩笑不谈
''But all kidding aside,
这是相同于...
in much the same way...
匠人曾被认为是直立人的
...that Homo ergaster is thought to be
另一个分支
a separate species from Homo erectus....''
什么
What?
他说"勃起"（erectus:直立人  还有勃起的意思）
He said "erectus."
你在开玩笑吗
You're kidding, right?
不  他是真的那样说
No, he really said it.
而当然有许多很大的差异...
''And while there are certainly vast differences...
介于这些中生代化石
...between these Mesozoic fossils
跟此直立人例子
and the example of Homo erectus....''
勃起？
Erectus?
同性恋（Homo:人属中的一支  也有同性恋的意思）
Homo.
没错
Right.
"用非常真实的方式
''ln a very real way,
我们可以将中生代时期
we can bring the Mesozoic Era
带入二十一世纪"
into the 21 st century.''
谢谢
Thank you.
真的很棒
Really great.
谢谢你们
Oh, thanks, guys.
我认为很精采
l thought it was wonderful.
我是杰维斯·欧伯劳 康乃尔大学
Jarvis Oberblau. Cornell.
你突显出来的议题
l mean, the ideas you put forth,
尤其是你是这样的年轻而且...
and from someone so young and....
好的  现在我们只是在握着手
Okay, now we're just holding hands.
好的  我们要去海滩了
Alrighty. We're gonna hit the beach.
演讲真的很棒
That was really great.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
是啊  而且很有趣
Yeah. Oh, and so funny.
放轻松点
Take it easy.
好的  谢谢  非常谢谢
All right, thanks. Thanks so much.
我无法告诉你
l can't tell you how much it means
你们在此对我意义有多大
that you were here.
你在开玩笑吗  我们不可能会错过的
You kidding? We wouldn't have missed it.
我回来了
l'm back.
好的  失陪一下好吗
Okay. Well, excuse me?
怎么样
Well?
你真是不可思议
You were incredible.
你完全迷住了他们了
You blew them away.
我无法告诉你在人群中
l can't tell you how great it was
看到你的脸有多棒
to look in the crowd and see your face.
我是说 你知道你嘴巴
l mean, did you know you were
在跟着我念吗
mouthing the words along with me?
我没有
l was not.
不  没关系
No, it's okay.
那让我觉得很像摇滚巨星
lt made me feel like a rock star.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我跟你是流行乐迷（groupie:想与流行乐队成员发生性关系的少女）
l'm your groupie.
我最好不要在房间里
Hey, l better not find you naked
发现你脱光光喔
in my hotel room.
哎呀  我又扯太远了
Look, l took it too far.
我不敢相信又在下雨了
l can't believe it's raining again.
真是不公平
lt's so unfair.
往好处想
Well, on the bright side,
就是我们不用看到...
now we won't have to see...
那些古生物学家脱掉上衣
...all these paleontologists with their shirts off.
不是你们
Not you guys.
你们还不错
You've got it going on.
我们今天要做什么呢
What will we do today?
他们楼下有游戏间
They have a game room downstairs.
有兵乓球还有其他的东西
They have Ping-Pong and stuff.
乒乓球  亲爱的  他们有乒乓球耶
Ping-Pong? Honey, they have Ping-Pong.
我们来玩
Let's play.
我想不好
l don't think so.
为什么不要
Why not?
你知道你得失心很重的
You know how competitive you get.
我以前说那样很可爱
And while l say it's cute,
可是别人都不同意  而且我在说谎
others disagree, and l'm lying.
我又不是永远都那样糟糕
l'm not always that bad.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
我们上次玩的时候发生什么事呢
What happened when we played last time?
我揍了你
l punched you.
还有呢
And?
还有菲比
Phoebe.
还有呢
And?
我把你们的头撞在一起
l clunked your heads together.
你在这里
There you are.
嘿  听着
Hey. Listen.
只要一停雨
As soon as it stops raining,
我们一定要去潜泳
we have got to go snorkeling.
有个小孩告诉我有海龟
Some kid told me about this sea turtle.
如果你对着他的脸吹气泡...
lf you blow bubbles in his face...
他会追着你跑喔
...he chases you.
我很抱歉  我不能去
l'm sorry, l can't.
我整个下午都要主持一个讨论组
l'm running a discussion group all afternoon.
没关系  我找别人去好了
That's okay. l'll find someone else to do it.
我是可以一个人去  但是...
l'd do it alone, but...
我不知道海龟
...l don't know what happens
如果抓到我会发生什么事
if the sea turtle catches you.
我觉得很糟糕
You know, l feel so bad.
我整趟旅途都没有跟你在一起
l haven't seen you this whole trip.
尤其是昨晚...
Especially last night--
不用担心  没关系
Don't worry about it. lt was fine.
我跟瑞秋玩得很开心
l end up had the best time with Rachel.
我只是为你难过
l just felt bad for you,
跟罗斯关在房间里赶演讲稿
stuck in that room working on Ross' speech.
事实上  还蛮好玩的
Actually, it turned out to be a lot of fun.
那至少
Oh, well, at least
我们都过得很愉快  不是吗
we're both having fun, right?
我们不在一起却很快乐  很怪吧
ls it weird that it's not with each other?
是啊
Yeah.
有一点  是啊
A little bit, yeah.
我想我们需要谈谈
l think we need to talk.
是啊  我想我们是需要
Yeah, l think we do.
谈什么呢
About what?
别这样  会很好玩的啦
Come on, you guys, it'll be fun!
好啦
All right.
不计分我才要玩
l'll play if we don't keep score.
那我们怎么知道谁赢呢
Well, then how do we know who wins?
没有人会赢
Nobody wins.
所以我们是四个输家  太好了
So we're just four losers. Super.
我不要跟她玩
Well, l'm not playing with her.
我不要玩了
l'm out.
我跟你玩
l'll play you.
好的
Okay.
你不知道你在做什么
You don't know what you're doing.
她会很疯狂的
She gets crazy.
这个疤痕是从猜字游戏来的
This scar? That's from Pictionary.
我想我会没事的
l think l'll be all right.
你想要先热身一下吗
You want to volley a bit for serve?
当然  如果你想要的话
Sure, if you want to.
对了  我很厉害的
Oh, by the way, l'm awesome.
亲爱的上帝  他们两是一样的
Oh, dear God, there's two of them.
你准备好要玩了吗
You ready to play?
当然了
Hell, yeah.
你有看过他这一面吗
Did you know this about him?
没有  我以为他跟你一样软弱
No idea. l thought he was soft like you.
想要更好玩点吗
Want to make it more interesting?
你想要多少呢
How much you thinking?
十块钱一局吗
Ten bucks a game?
加到五十块钱好了
Make it 50.
我加到一百块钱
l'll make it 1 00.
一千...
One thousand--
好了
Okay!
我们掷硬币来决定谁先开球
We'll flip to see who goes first.
你有硬币吗
You got a quarter?
没有  你们两个女生谁有硬币呢
No. Either of you girls got a quarter?
亲爱的  把这种骂人的话都用到他身上
Honey, try to focus the trash talk on him.
莫妮卡  你来猜
Monica, you call it.
正面  不  背面  正面
Heads. No, tails! Heads!
背面
Tails.
机率有这样低吗
Oh, what are the chances?
我得分
My point!
不  我可不这么认为
Oh, no, l don't think so.
根据乒乓球的规则
According the standard rules:
若参赛者
lf at any time a player
在任何时间将没握球拍的手...
uses his nonracket-bearing hand...
碰触到球桌表面
...to touch the playing surface,
将不算得分
he or she forfeits the point.
他曾经是律师
He was a lawyer.
东岸的天气十分良好
All the East Coast is having beautiful weather.
在纽约是华氏七十二度 而且阳光普照
ln New York, it's 72 and sunny.
气象婊子
Weather bitch.
门没锁
lt's open.
嗨  乔伊
Hi, Joe.
嘿
Hey.
怎么了  一切都还好吗
What? ls everything okay?
查莉跟我分手了
Charlie and l broke up.
不  为什么
No. Why?
嗯  她说我们没有任何共同点
Well, she said we have nothing in common.
这真是胡说
That's crazy.
不  是真的  我们没有任何共同点
No, it's not. We have nothing in common.
是啊  没错
Yeah, that's true.
是啊
Yeah.
她应该跟像是
l mean, she should be
罗斯那样的人在一起 你知道的
with someone more like Ross. You know,
他也会用那些很难的字眼
l mean he uses all those big words too.
天啊  聪明的人真是无趣
Man, smart people are dull.
嗯  是啊
Well, hey!
好了  瑞秋
Okay, Rach.
我觉得好蠢  你知道吗
l feel so stupid, you know?
为什么我一直都喜欢不适合我的女生呢
Why do l keep going after the wrong girls?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
喔  少来了
Oh, come on.
我是说  有你
l mean, there's you,
然后是查莉
then there's Charlie.
这就像是...我到底是哪根筋不对呢
lt's like.... What the hell's my problem?
我只是...
l just....
或许你并没有一直都
Okay. Maybe you're not always
在追不适合你的女生
going after the wrong girl.
我告诉你  瑞秋
l'm telling you, Rach,
查莉并不适合我
Charlie is not right for me.
我不是在说她
l'm not talking about her.
是喔  那是谁呢
Well, then, who?
那个我上个月约过的女服务生吗
The waitress l went out with last month?
你知道吗  算了
You know what? Forget it.
不...
No, no, no, no.
你是在说谁呢
Who are you talking about?
不  我不...
No, l don't--
事实上我并不知道
l actually don't know
我在说什么  所以...
who l'm talking about, so....
好的
Okay.
嗯
Yeah.
我要去看看有没有办法
Well, l'm gonna go see
再订到另一间房间
if l can get a room for tonight.
待会见
And l'll see you later.
是啊  好的
Yeah, sure. Okay.
你喜欢我
You like me?
好吧
Okay.
我们不要过度渲染这件事
Let's not make a big thing about this.
这是一件大事
lt's a huge thing!
你很不合作喔  乔伊
Okay, not working with me, Joe.
听着  事情事这样的
Look, here's the thing.
最近  我有些想法
Lately, l have been having thoughts.
应该说是冥想
Musings, if you will.
多久了呢
Well, for how long?
大概只有一个月
Oh, only like a month.
一个月
A month?
嗯...
Well--
小声点
Dial it down.
或许只是一些疯狂的想法
Listen, maybe they're crazy thoughts,
但是有时候我就是会想啊
but sometimes l do.
我一直在想我们之间的可能性
l have been thinking about, you know, us.
好的  现在音调提高一点
Okay, dial it up a little.
你说的对  好的
Oh, you're right. Okay.
我只有一个问题 该死
l just have a question. Shoot.
你倒底是在做什么
What the hell are you doing?
我在努力不做任何事情
l'm not trying to do anything.
只是当我们在一起时
lt's just, we have such a good time
非常地快乐  你知道吗
when we're together, you know?
你难道都没有好奇过
And l mean, aren't you just a little curious
那会是怎样吗
what it would be like?
我好奇过  我就跟...
Am l curious? l mean, l'm as curious as...
乔治一样好奇
...George!
谁
Who?
好奇乔治啊 你知道的
Curious George! You know,
那只猴子还有那个戴黄帽的男人
the monkey and the guy with the yellow hat.
我当然记得
Yes. Of course. l remember him.
他还有个纸路线图
He had a paper route.
是啊  没错
Yeah, he did.
这就是我说的
See, this is what l'm talking about.
我知道  我们棒透了
No, l know. We're great!
但是瑞秋  不  不能这样的
But, Rach, no, this can't happen.
不能有一点点机会吗
Can't it just happen a little bit?
不  一点也不行
No! lt can't happen at all!
为什么不行
Why not?
因为  你看
Because, look,
我最希望事情是这样了  好吗
no one wants this to happen more than me, okay?
我在我脑海中已经幻想过
l have gone over this moment
这情节一百次了
in my head 100 times...
而且我从没拒绝过
...and not once did l ever say no.
我不能这样对罗斯
l couldn't do it to Ross.
但之前却不是这样
But that wasn't gonna stop you before.
我知道...
l know. l know...
但是在那之后我想了很多
...but l've thought about it a lot since then,
这是不对的
and it just wouldn't be right.
我很抱歉
l'm sorry.
我也很抱歉
l'm sorry too.
天啊  我不应该说出来的
Oh, God, l shouldn't have said anything.
不...
No, no.
别这样  我们没事的
No, no, no, no. Hey, we'll be fine.
就像你所说的  这没有什么
Like you said, it's no big deal.
没错
lt's not a big deal.
没有什么
No big deal.
真的是没有什么
lt's so not a big deal.
待会见  好啰
l'll see you later. All right, hey.
好的  太好了
Okay, great.
好的...
Okay--
真抱歉  我想...
Oh, l'm sorry, l think--
我想那可能没有上台
l think that may have missed the table.
是吗
Oh, do you?
是的 是吗
Yeah. Do you?
是的
Yeah!
你真的认为他这样很有魅力吗
You really find this attractive on him?
是的
Oh, yeah.
你要告诉我你现在没有
Are you telling me you're not even a little turned on
被莫妮卡撩的心痒痒的
by Monica right now?
这是婚后我第一次觉得
This is the first time in our marriage
我是比较有魅力的那一个
that l've felt like the more attractive one.
好了  加油  迈克
All right, come on, Mike.
你可以打败她的
You can beat her.
把她打得落花流水
Knock that dog off her head.
该死的
Damn it!
我跟他上床哦
l sleep with him!
局点
Game point.
别太骄傲
Don't get too cocky.
记住上局是我赢的
Remember, l won the last one.
喔  对了
Oh, by the way,
输给一个女生感觉如何呢
how did that feel, losing to a girl?
你应该先照照镜子
You should look in the mirror
再这样说
before you call yourself that.
不  不  不
No! No! No!
而就是这样结束了
And that's how it's done.
好了
Okey-dokey.
你们都各赢了一局
You've each won a game,
而我感觉好像是失去了一年的生命
and l've lost what's felt like a year of my life.
每个人都可以跟一个赢家回家
Everybody goes home a winner.
三战两胜
Best of three?
我就是这样想
That's what l'm thinking.
我应该运用我的隐形术
Should l use my invisibility
来打击罪犯还是干坏事
to fight crime or for evil?
开球吧  木头人
Serve the ball, chump.
"开球吧  木头人"
''Serve the ball, chump.''
好的  重披战袍会更好
Okay, better comebacks,
迈克  重披战袍会更好
Mike. Better comebacks.
我是说
l'm just saying,
我在阿尔刚金有间小木屋
l have a cabin in the Adirondacks.
如果你有想要远离尘嚣
lf you ever want to get away from the city, well,
那将会是...
that'd be...
多俏皮啊
...just nifty.
嗯  我现在事情是蛮多的
Well, l've kind of got a lot on my plate right now.
不是说我不喜欢
Not that l wouldn't love a weekend
跟陌生男人到乡间度周末
in the country with a strange man.
杰维斯
Jarvis?
喔  你回来了
Oh, you're back.
这是我老婆  南西
This is my wife, Nancy.
少来了
Well, get out!
罗斯  我可以跟你谈谈吗
Ross? Can l talk to you for a minute?
当然了
Yes, please.
发生什么事呢
So, what's going on?
嗯  乔伊跟我分手了
Well, Joey and l broke up.
我的天啊  发生了什么事
Oh, my God. What happened?
乔伊是个好男人
Joey is a great guy...
但是我们就是...
...but we're just--
我们很不一样了
We're so different.
就像是在你演讲的时候
l mean, like, during your speech,
他一直在笑"直立人"
he kept laughing at ''Homo erectus.''
我就知道是他
l knew that was him!
反正  我只是...
Anyway, l just....
我想这样是最好的
l think it's for the best.
嘿  你还好吗
Hey. Hey, you okay?
还好
l guess.
还有...
There was....
还有另外一个原因
There was another reason that
让我跟乔伊分手的
l thought it was time to end it with Joey.
我开始发觉
l started to realize that
我对另外一个人有感觉
l was having feelings for someone else.
好的  盖勒  研讨会的最后一天了
Okay, Geller. Last day of the conference.
你知道主讲人会被怎样的
You know what happens to the keynote speaker.
克雷克教授
Professor Klarik,
我们正在谈话当中
we're in the middle of a conversation here.
不能等会再丢他进游泳池吗
Can't you throw him in the pool later?
或是把你们俩都丢进去
Or we could throw you both in now.
先生们  拜托
Okay, gentlemen, please.
我们会不会太老了呢
Aren't we a little old for this?
我是说我们是科学家  好吗
l mean, we're scientists, all right?
我们都有学术素养
We're academics...
而且最重要的
...and most importantly,
你们必须要先捉住我们
you will have to catch us first.
跑  跑  跑
Go! Go! Go!
好的  又平手了  四十一比四十一
Okay, so it's tied again, 41 to 41 .
好的  听着  够了
Okay, look, enough is enough.
不
No.
我剩下两分就可以打败他了
l just have two more points to beat him.
莫妮卡  一小时前你就这样说了
Monica, that was also true an hour ago!
拜托  瞧瞧你自己
l mean, please, look at you.
你的手都起水泡了
Your hand is blistered,
你连站都站不住
you can barely stand,
你的头发都没法说了
your hair is inexplicable!
你已经证明
You've already proven
你跟他一样好了
you're just as good as he is.
我们已经错过晚餐预约
We missed our dinner reservations,
所以我们就上楼去...
so let's just go upstairs...
点客房服务
...order room service,
洗个澡  然后剃你光的头发
take a shower and shave your head!
我不能这样走掉
l can't just walk away.
我已经投入四小时了
l've put in four hours.
当你娶我的时候
You knew this about me
你就知道我是这样的
when you married me.
你答应无论我生病
You agreed to take me
或是健康都要照顾我的
in sickness and in health.
这就是我的病
Well, this is my sickness!
那洁癖呢
What about the obsessive cleaning?
那只是好习惯
That's just good sense.
你还好吗
You okay?
亲爱的  我还好
No, honey, l'm okay.
甩一甩就好了
Shake it off.
哎  别哆嗦...
Oh, no shaking....
我的天  我不能玩了
Oh, my God. l can't play.
所以你要弃权
So you forfeit?
迈克赢了吗
Mike wins?
我不敢相信  我输了
l can't believe it. l lost.
不  你没有
No, you didn't.
什么
What?
因为我要帮你玩
Because l'm gonna play for you.
你不能这样做
You can't do that.
没关系
lt's okay.
我不在乎到底是打败他们其中哪个
l don't care which of them l beat.
好的  我们要把那个球拍带回家  先生
Okay, we're taking that paddle home, mister.
亲爱的  你没有必要这样做
Honey, you don't have to do this.
是的  我有必要
Yes, l do.
我或许无法理解
l may not understand
你为什么一定要赢...
why you have to win so badly...
但是如果这对你很重要
...but if it's important to you,
对我就很重要
it's important to me.
因为我爱你
Because l love you.
但是你很逊啊
But you suck.
不客气  甜心
You're welcome, sweetheart.
好的  我们快玩吧
All right, let's get this over with.
突然死亡法
Sudden death.
赢得这一分的人就算赢了
Whoever wins this point, wins.
好的
Okay.
天啊  你真棒
Oh, my God. You're good.
这就像是看色情片一样
lt's like watching porn.
而这就是这样结束的
And that's how it's done.
我的天啊... 这实在太惊人了
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. That was so amazing.
嗯  你是何时...
Well, when did you--?
等等  我差点忘了  失败者
Hold on, l almost forgot. Loser.
你是什么时候开始不逊的
When did you stop sucking?
我从来就不逊
l never sucked.
我只是不想让你...
l just didn't want you...
为什么
Why?
我不知道
l don't know.
这真是太棒了
Well, this is so great.
现在我们可以参加双打比赛了
Now we can enter doubles tournaments.
这就是为什么
That's why.
他们还在找我们吗
They still looking for us?
是的
Yeah.
酒保说
The bartender said
他们分成两组搜索队伍
they split up into two search parties.
草食性组跟肉食性组
The herbivores and the carnivores.
我们这一组并不是最酷的
You know, we, as a group, are not the coolest.
哦  小心
Oh, look out.
我想他们没有看到我们
l don't think they saw us.
没错
l don't think they did.
我刚刚要开始告诉你一些事
So l started to tell you something earlier.
还有其他的原因
There was another reason that
让我跟乔伊分手的
l realized it was time to end it with Joey.
我有点感觉到
l kind of realized
我开始对某人...
l was starting to have feelings...
有一些感觉
...for someone else.
我可以问是谁吗
And can l ask who?
我想你知道是谁
l think you know.
我想我也是
l think l know too,
但过去我对这种事的判断
but l've been really wrong
都是错的  所以...
about this stuff in the past, so....
我很抱歉  我们不能
l'm sorry, we can't.
好的  好的
All right. All right.
我是说 你才刚跟我
l mean, you just went out
最好的朋友交往过
with my best friend, you know?
我只是认为
l just think
这会是个很不好的主意
it would be a really, really bad idea.
或许不会  我是说...
Or not. l mean--
什么
What?